

Gregory Parakhnenko

E-mail: parahnen@gmail.com Phone: +38(050)997-66-69

+38(068)404-14-14

Skype:

gregoriy.parakhnenko

Objective

The scope of IT - an area which has no limits for self-development, which is why I chose it.

I really like web development, so I try to constantly move in this direction, constantly evolving, deepening their knowledge and explore new directions.

Today, I want to get the post html developer, in order to succeed in this field, and to gain experience in the IT team.

Skills

- HTML5/CSS3;
- JavaScript/jQuery.

Frameworks:

- Bootstrap, ZURBfoundation, Skeleton;
- · AngularJS, React JS.

Preprocessors:

• SASS/SCSS/LESS.

Software:

- Sublime text 3, Brackets, Notepad++, Atom;
- GitHub, Git Bash, Node;
- Corel Draw, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, I nkscape;
- SolidWorks, Компас, T-Flex, TopSolid, Unigraphics

Work experience

Bisa Group

Feb 2016 — Dec 2016

Designer

- · Create 3D visualizations serviced enterprises to further their reconstruction and modernization
- Creating Interactive SVG-visualization, to connect to a remote control system and the control of production "Overvis"

Gregory Parakhnenko

PE "East"

Oct 2015 — Feb 2016

Manager

- Organize and run workshops for metal working "from scratch"
- · The selection and purchase of technological equipment
- Search, purchase and organization of materials supply

Ltd. "UBS-XXI"

Dec 2014 — Oct 2015

IT manager

- Development of new equipment
- · Starting an internet sales
- Website Designing Company
- Create 3D visualizations serviced enterprises to further their reconstruction and modernization
- · Search perspective directions of development

Ltd. "Northern Crown"

Sep 2013 — Dec 2014

Chief designer

- First Deputy Director
- Management Department
- · Accompanying production
- Search perspective directions of development
- · Development of new models of equipment and completion of existing

Ltd. "Northern Crown"

Jul 2013 — Sep 2013

Engineer

- Development of design documentation
- Accompanying production

SE KhMP "FED"

Dec 2012 — Jul 2016

Head of Office management tool

The subordinates were group "repair devices", consisting of professionals working specialties and a group of engineers, a total of 10-12 people. The main task was to ensure uninterrupted production workshop tools and industrial equipment

SE KhMP "FED"

Apr 2012 — Dec 2012

Engineer

- Development of technological processes.
- · Logistics tool in the workplace.

Education

Aircraft engine manufacturing technology

Sep 2004 — Feb 2012

National Aerospace University "KhAI"

Department of aviation engines

Specialist degree in "aircraft engine manufacturing technology"

Gregory Parakhnenko 2

Additional education

- I got a specialist degree in "Aircraft engine manufacturing technology"
- Effective communication (Kharkiv, Ukraine) Year-End 2013
- Occupational safety and fire safety (Kharkiv) Year-End 2016
- HTML-Academy (free course) 2016
- Fundamentals of Software Testing from Lviv IT School (prometheus.org.ua)
- HTML, CSS and Javascript for web developers (coursera.org)
- Learn JavaScript (www.codecademy.com)
- Make a Website (www.codecademy.com)
- jQuery (www.codecademy.com)
- Learn Sass (www.codecademy.com)

Gregory Parakhnenko 3